本作品由NORM 荣誉出品
下载后仅供学习交流,严禁用于商业途径
压制:阿聪锋狂   双显&特效字幕:Risa Miriam
各位听众，今晚疑幻疑真的节目又开始了
Listeners, stay tuned for tonight's Ghost Story
这一个世界有很多不可思议的事情发生
Incredible things happen anytime anywhere
真是信不信由你
Believe it or not
首先要接听的电话是一位 自称曾经撞过鬼的朋友打来
Now on the line is one who claims to have seen a ghost
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是来坐车的
I come for a ride
刚才我有没有撞到你？
Did I hit you just now?
就当没有好了，开车啦！
Just drive the car
你是怎样搅的？
What's wrong with you?
你还不来，那两个女人要走了
Where the hell are you? They're tired of waiting
我知，我正在开车出来， 多等我一会儿，OKAY？
I'll be there soon, OK?
你们两个做什么？
Hey, what are you two up to?
识趣一点，别碍事
Let them be, let's go
走吧！
O.K.
把丝巾还给我
Give me back the scarf
你可以走了
You may leave now
你不会介意吧？
Do you mind?
通常在这种情况下，我都不会介意
Normally, I don't
你叫CECILIA？
Are you Cecilia?
为什么这么晚一个人在这里？
Why are you alone at this hour?
我想自杀
I want to end my life
好主意！我带你去一个地方自杀，走吧！
Good idea! Let me take you to a place to do it
鸡翼，一大群美女等了你一个晚上， 快要骚了
The girls have been waiting all night
我先到那边去
Let me go there first
那边是守斋的
That side is for gays only
人真多
What a crowd
这个是MEIMEI，这个是MORMOR
This is Mei Mei, this is Mor Mor
MEIMEIMORMOR
MEl MEl MOR MOR
HELLO！
HELLO!
我们公司的美术总监，鸡翼
Our Art director Chicken Wing
鸡翼！？
Chicken Wing!?
我姓戚，叫近荣
My real name is Chi Ken Wing
CHICKENWING
CHICKEN WING
笑什么笑？我有叫你笑吗？
Laugh? Did I tell you to laugh?
你先坐一会
Have fun
坐下，走什么走？
Sit down, don't go away?
兄弟，你现在是找广告模特儿， 不是找老婆，明不明白？
You're looking for a model, not a wife, understand?
你心目中的白雪公主，在这一个世界上 是不存在的，大爷
There's no such Show Whitein this world, my dear!
谁说的？你看看那一边
Why not? Look over there
那边？
There?
那边有两个男人在亲嘴，你要不要？
You like those two menkissing over there.
在那边
She's there
上！
Come on!
干什么？
What are you doing?
他找到他的女朋友
He found his dream girl
鸡翼的品味好高
Chicken Wing's taste is pretty selective
在那里
Over there
阿婶，请问有没有一个白衣服的 女孩子进了去？
Madam, didyou see a girl in white skirt come in?
看看怎么样？
Let's see how she looks
是啊！很快就出来了  谢谢你！
Yes, she's coming out now Thank you
我们伟大的美术总监，AVANTI…
Oh, my dear art director, Avanti...
看看她怎么漂亮？  有型一点！
She must be stunning Wonderful!
COMEON…
COME ON...
真艳丽
Really charming
美得我要哭
Charming like hell
吓得我傻了，你今天晚上一定是撞鬼
You must have met a ghost to-night
250C.C
250C. C
那一个女孩子是谁？
Who's this girl?
漂不漂亮？
What do you think?
漂亮
Yes, beautiful?
正…！
Great...
这一个就是你的梦中情人？
Your dream girl?
PERFECT，正点得很
Perect, truly perfect!
我们是不是老朋友？
Are we good friends?
老朋友！？
Good friends?
看情况而定
It depends
是老朋友就同我去沙田找找她
If we are, help me to find her
我真是无知，无缘无故跟你来，这么无聊
I must be a fool to help you
前面有两幢大厦，一定住在那里
She must live somewhere in one of the buildings
请问你有没有见过这一个女孩子？
Excuse me, have you seen this girl?
没见过，没有见过
Never
是不是在那里？
Are you sure?
请问你有没有见过这个女孩子？
Have you seen this girl, please?
谢谢！   正点！真是正点！
Thank you Great! Fantastic!
没有这一个人   谢谢！
She doesn't exist Thank you
不用客气
Don't mention it
鸡翼，我求求你别这么无聊好不好？
Chicken Wing, Let's forget it O. K?
我哮喘啦！我受不了  走吧…！
I'm getting a sore throat Let's go...
臭小子，你敢搅我的车子？
How dare you scratch my car!
把球还给我，还给我！
Give me back the ball!
不要这么不守规矩
Hey! Cut it out
臭小子！
Bastard!
婆婆
Hello.
请问找那一位？
What do you want?
请问你有没有见过这一个女孩子？
I'm looking for this lady
没有这一个人
No such lady here
不是啊！我认得她这一件衣服
I recognize her white dress
请你告诉我，她住在那里？
Please tell me where she is
你找她有什么事？
Why do you want to see her?
没什么，她借了我的衣服，我想她还给我
I want to get my coat back, I lent her
是几时的事？
When do you lend it her?
前天晚上
Two night ago
前天晚上！年轻人，我告诉你
Two night ago? Young man, listen.
前一个月，她走出这条马路被车撞死了
She was killed in a car accident last month
你撞鬼呀！
you must come across her spirit
我撞鬼！鬼有这么漂亮吗？
Spirit? She must be joking?
婆婆，别骗我了，开门吧！我不信的
Granny, don't joke with me. Open the door please
好吧！你自己到里面去问她好了
Well, come inside & ask her then
年轻人，你这么渴望想见她
Young man, if you want to see her
去华人永远坟场1444号见她吧！
Go to No.1444.Chinese Perpetual Cemetery
谢谢婆婆
Thank you granny
你近来时运低，所以整天撞鬼
Seeing a ghost means, you've bad luck lately
现在带你去见一个大师，教你趋吉避凶
Let me introduce you to a fortune teller
是什么人？
Who is he?
走吧！他的电脑算命很灵的
He uses computers to tell fortune
大师兄，我的朋友来了
Master, I bring my friends here
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
他是戚近荣，男性，一九六…
Chi Ken Wing, male,196...
一呀！一
1! 1
一九六一年，六月六日凌晨六时出生
Born on 6th June,1961,at 6 a.m.
他的年纪是三十，不…
He's 30,no...
是二十七岁
27 years old
他的运气很不好
He has bad luck recently
头上的光是灰色的
His halo looks dark
还有一道红色的光射进他的头里
& a redlight has entered into his head
我看他一个月内就会有桃花劫
Within this month, he'll encounter a tragedy
还有血光之灾，要特别小心
Perhaps a disaster. Be careful, Sir
这个家伙会不会是猛鬼缠身？
Will he be possessed by an unclean spirit
目前看起来还没有
Not at the present
不过，你要少滚一点
But don't fool around so much
有什么方法可以化解呀？大师
Master, can we do anything about it
有，这是一条古老的呢珠
Yes, this is a holy charm!
能够帮助你解决魔障
It may keep you away from the devil
但是你要多跟那些好运的人在一起
and be sure you stick with lucky people
这样才能够消除灾难
It helps to diminish the possibility of tragedy
那么我跟她算不算是行运呀？
Are we these lucky people?
你头顶发的是白色的光
Your halo is bright
你没有桃花劫，不用怕
It's alright. No sweat
我！？
Me?
是啊！她发的是金色的光，吉星高照
Herhalo is golden, means luck is on her side
我想你要是跟她多亲近点的话，会有好处的
Stick with her. It'll be good for you
好好保护
Value her, she can protect you
我知道，谢谢大师！
Thank you, master!
你妈咪，爹哋结婚三十周年纪念，签了它
It's your parents'30th anniversary. Sign it
幸亏有你看着
Thanks for reminding me that
要不然他们以为生块叉烧好过生我
Otherwise. They'll kill me
谢谢你！
Thank you
THANKYOU！
THANK YOU!
阿ANN，坐下！
Ann Sit Down
干什么？
Why?
坐下！
Sit down!
HAPPYBIRTHDAYTOYOU
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU
你怎么知道我生日？
How do you know it's my birthday?
成班同事送东西给你，你以为我是盲的
I saw them sending yoou the present
干什么？
What's matter?
我们今天晚上在CASABLANCA吃饭，你一起来
Will you join our party at the Casablanca to-night
好！
Okay!
真的！？
Serious?
HAPPYBIRTHDAY…
HAPPY BIRTHDAY...
你不用了
No need!
你什么时候带我到美国去看你的妈咪嗲哋？
When do I go to USA to see your parents?
他们好凶的，你不怕吗？
They're fierce. They'll scare you
儿子这么凶我也不怕
Their son doesn't scare me.
怎么会怕他们？
Why should I be scared of them?
这是什么？
What's this?
灵符，在日本买的
A Buddha statue from Japan
上一个礼拜DAVID去日本买衣服
David bought it for me
我特地请他在雷门观音寺请回来
He went Japan shopping last week
八卦
Superstitious
全都是为了你
It's all because of you
你妈咪快生日了，你想送什么给她？
What would you like to buy for your mom's birthday
开车呀！这条马路不是你的
Hey, this is not your private road!
很了不起吗？
What's the big deal?
挡着路…
Get lost...
开车呀！
Move!
Go
我今天不去吃饭，对不起！
Sorry. I can't join your party to night
你还是整天想着那个女鬼
You're still thinking of her
还给我！
Give it back to me!
我都不明白你耍什么花样？
Stop making a fool of yourself
阿ANN的爸爸专程从美国飞回来见你
Ann's dad came over from England to see you
分明是全心全意跟你来真的
Obviously hey're serious about you
你就不是，整天想着玩那只女鬼， 不知道有什么益处？
What good does it bring to keep on thinking that spirit
她不是女鬼，我昨天才见到她
She's not a spirit. I saw her yesterday
你醒醒好不好？这全都是你的幻觉
Wake up please, it's your imagination again
你亲眼看过她的坟墓，她已经死了
She's dead. You've already seen her grave
她死了
She's dead!
很渺茫呀！
Where the hell is it?
就在这里附近
It's somewhere around here
你记得几多号码？
Can you remember the number?
记得，是1444号
Yes, it's 1444
鸡翼，你不是吧！1444？你看看
Chicken Wing? 1444? Are you sure?
是个阿婆
It's a granny
你们两个在这里干什么？
What are they doing here?
大叔，我们是来找人的
We're looking for someone
是呀？有没有德国鬼妹？
Is there a german girl here?
这一个房子已经半年没有人住了
This flat has been vacant for the last 6 months
不是啊！我前天才跟一个阿婆在这里聊过天
lmpossible. I talked to an old woman here 2 days ago
你不相信吗？
You don't believe it?
好吧！我开门让你们两个进去看看
Go in & see for yourseleves
看看你就会死心
You'll see
你是个知识份子，为了一个不明来历的 女孩子疯了真是不值得
It's not worth it to waste your time on her
我也有自己的事情要做
I have my own business to do
对不起！
Sorry!
你说，那里有这么理想的女孩子，你说
Tell me, does the perfect girl exist?
有
Yes
有呀！
She does exist
有就快点出来
Tell her to show up then
小心走路！
Watch out
早晨！先生，欢迎光临
good morning. Sir, welcome in
小姐，请问你有没有看到一个穿 粉红色衣服的女孩子进来
Did you see a girl with a pink coat come in
不就是我
It was me
我不是说红色，我说的是粉红色
I mean pink not red
在你后面
She's behind you
我明明看到一个粉红色衣服的女孩子
I saw a girl in pink coat for sure
你全看到了
Take a look then
谢谢！
Thank you
CECILIA
他还没有走，他就在门口
He's still at the entrance
O.K
O.K.
我明明看到一个穿粉红色衣服的女孩子
I'm sure that she had come here
我都说没有，如果你不是买东西就请你出去
Please leave if you're not buying anything
先生，什么事？
What's matter, young man
没什么，我找人
I'm looking for someone
找到了没有？还不走
Have you found her? Go away
对不起！
Sorry!
下班了吧！
Time off
别毛手毛脚！
Don't be so rude
什么？
What?
你真坏！
You're bad!
早晨！
Good morning!
怎么又是你？
You again?
送给你的
It's for you
我知道你知道她在什么地方
I'm sure you know where she is
我也知道你是个好人
I'm sure you're aa kind girl too
你说错了，我不是善男信女
Wrong. I'm not that kind
你也见过我的男朋友，你还不走你会很麻烦
You met my boyfriend. Please go now Otherwise you'll be in trouble
那好吧！
Alright
CECILIA，好刺激呀！那个男孩子又来了， 你见见他
Cecilia, he came again. You should see him this time
好吧！
Okay!
跟她通完了电话啦！
You finished the call with her?
什么…？
What?
什么，我早说你一定知道她在那里
Well, as I said, you know where she is
我找了她很久
I've tried hard to find her
我不知道
I don't know
IDON’TKNOW
I DON'T KNOW
她在这里喝茶？
Is she in this coffee shop now?
不是我说的，是你自己说的
You said so, not me
是我说的
I said it
请借朵花来用一用？
May I have your flower?
这里不准搭台的
There's no table sharing in this place
你的衣服已经还给你了
I've already returned you the coat
我想我要一个更加好一点的解释
How about an explanation?
第一次见到你就被你亲得昏头转向
First time I met you why did you kiss me
然后告诉我，你死了
Then you told me you were dead
一会儿又看到你的坟墓
Then I saw your grave
究竟是什么意思？
What does it all mean?
有脚就不会是鬼
You've got feet. So you're not a ghost
最多我多谢你送我一程
Anyway, thank you for your ride
我男朋友来了，他不喜欢我跟陌生人一起
My boyfriend's coming. He hates seeing me with a stranger
欢迎呀！曹先生
Welcome, Mr. Tsao
喂！
Hey! Cut it out
曹先生，这边请！
Mr. Tsao, this way, please
你最好快点走
You'd better leave now
干什么？
What are you doing?
搭台又关你的事？
Is that any of your business?
是呀，搭台又关你事？
He's right, is that any of your business?
送给你
It's for you
多谢三哥！
Thank you, Sam
怎么你的朋友走得这么快？
Why does your friend leave so soon?
他不是我的朋友，他没位子来搭台而已
He's not my friend. He just wanted to share the table
阿豹
Ah Pow
是！
Yes
CECILIA的朋友没有台子，替我招呼他一下
Cecilia's friend has no seat. Find him one
三哥，不用了
Sam, forget it
干什么？
Hey, what are you doing?
你究竟想怎样？
What do you want?
快走！
Go now!
擦伤了
It's bleeding
CECILIA
我…
I...
我什么？
What?
其实那一个人很喜欢你
He's really devoted to you
如果有一个人这么喜欢我
If someone loves me like that
我为他死也甘心
I'd do anything for him
他被三哥打，伤得很厉害
He was seriously hurt by Brother Sam
现住在法国医院，你去探他一下
He's now in French Hospital, go & see him
丫头，你懂什么？
You're too young to understand
我是不懂，但我知道你穿白衣服 比穿黑衣服好看
But I understand you look much better in white than black
钓了多少鱼？
Fishing?
你醒啦？我睡着了也不知道
I didn't realize that you'd waken up
我煲了些皮蛋瘦肉粥给你
I've prepared some pork congee for you
我去拿点水
I'll get some water
你以后不要再来找我
Don't look for me again
为什么？
Why?
不要问为什么，那天晚上的事忘记了它
Don't ask why, just forget everything
为了那一个男人？
Because of that man?
他配不上你
He's not worthy of you
配不配是我的事，你无权过问
That's my affair. You've no right to stop me
你不可以阻止我来找你
You've no right to stop me seeing you either
如果你再找我，下一次就不止 躺医院这么简单
Next time you won't end up in hospital. Don't be stubborn
我一定会再来找你
I'll find you again
三哥，拍张照
Brother Sam,
陈律师
Solicitor Chan
三哥，恭喜你！
Congratulations!
今天法庭正式通过，你是财产合法继承人
The court announced your right of succession to-day
令尊的亿万遗产永远属于你
The vast lagacy of your father belongs to you for good
你这一荸律师费也赚了不少
You also made a fortune from the legal fees
勉强够第二个家的开支啦！
Just enough to cover the expenses for my second family
阿三，你老爸的身体一向很好
Sam, your father was in excellent health
为什么突然间会死了？
why did he die so suddenly
是这样的，他是自杀的
He committed suicide
自杀！？
Committed suicide
他最近两单大生意都亏得很厉害， 损失了差不多一亿元
He lost almost a $100 million in 2 recent deals
他老人家一时看不开就…
Maybe he became morose, so...
没理由，曹伯伯一向都很乐观
Impossible, he was always so optimistic
你醉了
You're drunk
我醉！？我是故意喝醉的
Drunk? I intended to get drunk
醉薰薰看这个世界才够可爱
So I can see the world in its good light
省得看清楚那些丑恶的面孔
& avoid seeing the bad faces so clearly
我们去跳舞
Let's dance
CECILIA，我跟你说心事，不要过去
Cecilia, I need to talk to your privately
三哥
Brother Sam,
今晚好多人都会来这儿的…
Many VIP are coming to-night...
林太太
Mrs Lin
三哥
Brother Sam,
好久不见
It's been a long time
有美女也不介绍我认识？
Why don't you introduce such a beautiful girl to me?
怎么敢不介绍给你认识？
How dare I not introduce to you
这一位就是香港最著名的钻石王老五， 曹立三公子
This is one of HK's most eligible bachelor, Sam Tsao
这一位就是新鲜出炉港姐谢宝珊小姐
This is the new Miss Hong Kong Tse Bao-shan
你们喝点什么？我去拿给你们
Let me fetch you some drinks
你们两个要乖一点
Don't be naughty
好啊！如果今天没有认识宝珊小姐
If I didn't meet you tonight
真是如入宝山空手回
lt'd be just like in a gold mine and coming out empty handed
跳舞表演
Dancing Show
玩玩而已，不要太认真
Don't take it seriously
你小心呀
Be careful
Linda，你没事吧？
Linda, are you alright?
曹立三这个人就是这样子， 贪新忘旧，始乱终弃
Sam Tso is a playboy. Forsakes the old for the new
如果我是你就一定敲他一大掣
If I were you I'd make a fortune out of him
你别胡说
Don't say that
我是过来人，十年前他爱我
I had this experience 10 years ago, way he loved me,
就比现在爱你更厉害
More passionate than he loves you now
我还替他生了一个女儿， 你还傻呼呼的  是吗？
I even gave birth to a daughter for him. Silly! Is that so?
八卦周刊全都爆出来了
It was revealed to the public by all the scandal magazines
麻烦你，扶扶她
Please help her
我才收了他六十万
I just received $600,000 only
你喝醉了
You're drunk
我没有醉
I am not
香港小姐谢宝珊为我们高歌一曲
Tonight, we've the honour to invite the New Miss H. K
我们用热烈掌声欢迎她
To sing a song for us,
没法，没法拒绝去想你
I can't stop thinking of you
曾努力来逃避，但我直到午夜仍想你
I tried, But I can't help it
你醉了
You're drunk
你可以走了，我明天打电话给你
You may leave. I'll call you tomorrow
宝珊，我要你今天晚上陪我，宝珊
Po-shan, I want you tonight
你躺好
Lie down
你今天晚上的一举一动令到我好满意
Your behaviour tonight impressed me
不过你最近有很多艳闻
But there's rumours about your love affairs lately
没有呀，三哥
It's not true, brother Sam
不过我不介意，反正全香港都知道
But I don't mind since the whole HK knows it
宝珊，我终于得到你了
Po-shan, I've got you
ILOVEYOU
I LOVE YOU
姜汤煲好了
The ginger soup is ready
替我倒掉它
Throw it away!
三姐
Maid Sha
对不起！
Sorry!
其实，你什么时候才可以摆脱那个坏蛋？
When are you going to leave that rascal?
算啦！不要再提
Forget it, please let's not talk about it
我有一样东西给你看
I have something to show you
你看
Look
怎么会有只白鸽？
Where did you catch this dove
你记得嘛？那时候你还不够四岁
Do you remember when you were small
我在大屿山的旧房子里面养了几只白鸽， 你好喜欢
We raised many doves in the old house in Lantau Island
记得
I remember
今天它自己飞进了我们的露台
This one flew on to our balcony today
我打算一会儿宰了它，用来煲汤给你喝
It should make a nice soup
不要…，这么残忍
Don't... don't be so cruel
整天困着它，好可怜的
It suffers being kept in captivity
小姐呀！我记起来了
Miss, I nearly forgot
刚才老人院有电话来，叫你去看看公公
Someones from the sanitorium called up
我想，他也没有多少日子了
Asked you to look up your Grandpa
你放心啦！
Don't worry
你飞吧！你干嘛不飞？
Fly away! Why don't you fly away?
给人困得太久，不会飞了是不是？
You're used to captivity. It's hard for you fly away
下来呀！我等你好久了
Come down! I've been here for ages
我好冷呀！
I'm terribly cold!
你的事不关我事
That is not my concern!
ILOVEYOU，ILOVEYOU
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU
我爱你呀！
I love you!
我不爱你
I don't love you
啊…！无心睡眠
I'm no mood for sleep...
啊…！脑交战
my brains is in a whirl
你干嘛又来找我？
Why are you looking for me again
我答应过你   你答应过我什么？
Because I promise I would What did you promise me?
来找你
To look for you again
你现在见到我了，你可以走了，拜拜！
You've found me now. You can go. Bye!
你画的？
You painted it?
替我签个名
Please autograph if for me
游车河好吗？
How about a drive in the car?
7楼E座？
7E?
记不起来
I can't remember
你想怎么样？
What do you want?
今天晚上没有月光
There's no moonlight tonight
音乐很好听吧？
But the music is good
那个恶男人睡了吗？
Is that guy in bed already?
他有没有像打我一样打你呀？
Does he beat you like he beat me?
他今天晚上不会打你吧？
I hope that he didn't beat you tonight
为什么那一次你装死来骗我？
Why did you pretend to be dead to deceive me?
如果再是像审犯一样审下去
If you're going to address me like a criminal
我会好像上次一样跳车走的
I'll jump out of the car like last time
我去后面，你不要看我
I'I go to the back. Don't look at
干什么？想强奸我？
You want to rape me?
是啊…？
Yes...
先不要看
Close your eyes
有卧底告诉我
A sry told me
今天是你农历二月十七日生日，是不是？
It's your birthday today, lunar 17th Feb.
许个愿
Make a wish.
你一点也不认真，当然吹不熄蜡烛
They won't blow out because you didn't make a serious wish
我不吹了
I give up
来吧！我替你把蜡烛点着，让你许愿
Let me relight them. Come on, make a wish
不用点，反正我吹了十几年蜡烛都没有灵过
Forget it. My wishes never come true
其实你有什么愿望？
Tell me, do you have any ambition
做歌星
To be a singer
站在这里，别动！
Stay there! Don't move!
预备，开始
Ready, go!
WOO…，无心睡眠
I'm no mood for sleep because...
WOO…，脑交战
My mind is in a whirl
踏着脚在怀念，昨天的你
remember the old days
夜是渗着前事全挥不去
I tap my feet just thinking about the past
若是你在明日能得一见
If I could see you tomorrow
就让我在怀内重得温暖
And feel the warmth of your arms
别这样
Stop it!
不要阻住我…
Don't stop me...
不要这样，好了…
Calm down
没事啦！
Alright!
我唱歌是不是很难听？
Did I sing that bad?
不是很难听
Not that bad
是好很难听
Just very bad bad
幸好我没有做歌星，不然更加失败
It's lucky that I'm not singer otherwise I'd be much more destructive now
你跟着这一个男人，你很失败
You're pretty destructive being with that guy
你好烦呀！
You're a nuisance!
我刚才是不是很疯？
You must have thought I was insane just now
不会
Not really
当我每次最开心的时候，这么快就完
Every time I feel happy, it has to come to an end.
多谢你的生日饼！
Thanks for the birthday cakes!
我们什么时候再见！
When can we meet again?
几时？
When?
我们…
We...
到此为止
We got to end it here
我第一次看到你笑
It's the first time I see you smile
傻子，我已经做了
Well, I've played the fool
歌又唱完，生日饼也送了
Sung stupid songs, sent birthday cakes.
我想我没有机会了
I don't have a chance, do I?
再见！
Goodbye!
我明天去找你？
Where can I see you?
九点钟在港外线码头见
See you midday at the pier tomorrow
干嘛这么晚才回来？三爷快要醒了
Where've you been. Master Sam is about to wake up
你快点到房里去
Hurry up & go in now
谢谢！
Thank you
这么早到那里去？
Where did you go so earily?
我出去跑步
Jogging
你的头还痛不痛？
You still have a headache
我的头怎么会痛？
I haven't got any headache
你别以为我昨天晚上真的醉了
I was never really drunk last night
你的事我全都知道
I know everything.
缠着你的那个小子在广告公司做事
That guy works for an advertising agency
拍什么薄荷酒广告是不是？
He want you to shoot a mint wine ad.
是呀！
Yes
下次我见到他缠着你，我就扭掉他的头
If I see him again, I'll chop his head off
是呀！扭掉他的头
Yes, chop his head off
别理这种人，休息一下
Never mind him, sleep a little more
我今天晚上要去泰国，两三天后才回来
Tonight I'm off to Thailand for 2or3 days
你叫阿泉两点半来接我，我多睡一会
Tell Ah Chuen to pick me up at 2:20. I need some more sleep
对不起！我迟到
Sorry. I'm late
我好像是约了你的姐姐
It seems that I dated your sis, not you
她没有空，我是她的妹妹
She's busy. I'm her younger sister
我现在去探我姐姐的公公
Let's go visit my sister'd grandpa
还将不死你
You've lost!
还死不了
Not yet
仪姐
Miss Yee
带金，我正在等你
Tai-kam, here you at last
带金？
Tai-kam? (means gold carrier,)
又说很了解我，连我的真名字也不知道
You said you knew all about me, you don't even know my real names
医生说你公公随时都会死去
The doctor said your grandpa could pass away anytime
所以叫你签一张丧事授权书
We'd like you to sign the funeral authorization form
不过，他一知道你今天会来， 不知道多开心
When grandpa heard you were coming, he was so excited
整天叫我拿套西装给他穿 这不就行了吗？婆婆
He asked me to find a suit for him How about that?
谢谢你！仪姐
Thank you, Miss Yee
人隔万重山…
Mountains separate us
公公
Grandpa
带金，你来了吗？
Tai-kam, you've really come
公公，你好帅，还结了领花
Grandpa, you look so handsome with the bow tie
我们到上面去
Let's go
这一位是…？
Who is this...
他是我的未婚夫，戚近荣
My fiance Chi Ken Wing
CHIKEN？CHICKEN不就是鸡
Chi Ken sounds like chicken
鸡先生是吗？
Mr Chicken?
阿公，你好！
How do you do, grandpa?
你在那里办事！
Where do you work?
他在我教的那一家小学做主任
He's the supervisor at the school where I teach
那就是鸡主任？
So. He's a supervising chicken
随便什么都好
Whatever you say
带金，你有什么带来给我吃？
Tai-kam, did you bring anything today?
有
Yes
未来孙女婿，推我回房聊天好不好？
My future grandson-in-law, let's go in & talk
行！
Sure!
未来孙婿，今天虽然是第一次见面
My future grandson-in-law, although it's the first time I see you
但是你都很合我的眼缘
I like you
我现在就将个心肝宝贝的孙女全交给你
Alright, I give my dearest grand-daughter to you
你要好好的照顾她才好
Promise me to take good care of her
我会的
I will
她从小就受苦，未曾享过一日福
She's suffered greatly since childhood
你要好好的待她才好
Promise me to be kind to her
男人大丈夫，握手为盟
We're men, shake on it
你们干什么？握完一次手又一次手
Why do you keep shaking hands?
男人说男人的事，女人问这么多干什么？
This is men's talk, nothing to do with women
公公
Grandpa
这里有些五加皮茶，你试试好不好喝
Here's some Ng Ka Pitea, Try it
五加皮茶？
Ng Ka Pi (Chinese wine) tea?
拿回来
Give back to me
他已经日子无多了， 他喜欢什么就成全他好了
Give him what he wants. He's not got long.
又要喝？
Again
不是，我想你拿去给我的老朋友试一下
No, let my good friends try some,
好呀！
Good idea
带金，你妈咪有没有来信？
Tai-kam, any letter from your mom?
有！
Yes
拿来给我看看
Give it to me
我念给你听
I'll read it to you
爸爸，你好嘛！我在美国生活很好， 不用挂念
Dad, how are you? I'm fine in the USA. Don't worry about me
餐厅人客很多，三个小孩也很听话
We've many customers in our restaurant and our 3 kids are very nice
而最少一个已在店内打点一切
The youngest one has started to help in the restaurant
最少的那一个才袛有四岁，怎么打点？
How come? He's only four
打点…？
Help...
让我来吧！
Let me...
小儿子在楼面跟洋小子玩，很开心
The youngest one enjoys playing with foreign kids
工作很忙，就此搁荸，就这么多
I'm very busy... Got to go
就这么多，没啦？
Is that all?
再者，还有呀！
Oh, yes
支票已交给鸡翼兑现，你向他查收便可
There's a cheque payable to Chicken Wing, get it from him
那钱呢？
Where's the money?
有，在这里，我怕你不方便，替你换好了
It is here. I've cashed it
一共是八百元，你点一点   八百
$800 you better check it 800
数目对了
It's correct
未来孙婿，这三百元就是我给你的见面利是
Take this $300 as good luck money, my future grandson-in-low
多谢公公！
Thank you, grandpa...
公公…
Grandpa...
带金
Tai-kam
我给你三百银做嫁妆
This $300 is your marriage dowry
公公，我会叫CHICKEN接你出去喝喜酒的
Grandpa,, Chicken and I will fetch you for the wedding
不用了，留个空位给我就行了
Not necessary, just leave a vacant seat for me
一叶轻舟去…
A boat is drifting away...
人隔万重山
moutains separate as...
鸟南飞
The birds fly to the South
公公，冷呀！你回到里面去
Grandpa, it's cold, go inside
鸟南返
The birds return to the South
鸟儿比翼何日再归还，哀我何孤单，何孤单
when the birds return to lament my loneliness, my loneloness
带金
Tai-kam
不知道是公公送我，还是我送公公？
I don't know whether he sees me off or I see him off
原来你妈咪住在纽约？我妈咪…
Your momlives in New York. My mom also...
我妈妈在十年前已经死了
Mom had been dead almost 10 years
对不起！
Sorry!
公公这么老了，无谓令他太担心
Grandpa is so old. I couldn't hurt him
说得是
Right
这两块玉是我爸爸临死之前送给我妈妈
These jades pieces was my father's gift to mom before he died
毋怨毋悔，莫失莫忘
NO REGRETS, AND NO BLAME
以前的人好像比较浪漫一点
It seems our ancestors were more romantic
喂！等等！
Wait!
等等！
尾班船已经开了，明天早上再来
The last ferry has gone. Come again tomorrow
那现在怎么办？带金小姐
What can we do now, Miss Tai-kam?
这么晚又这么大雨，到那里去找酒店？
Where can we find a hotel in this weather
我带你去一家不用花钱的酒店
I'll take you to a hotel free of charge
酒店呀？
Hotel?
这里！？
Here!?
是呀！
Yes!
先点火
Light a fire
有火水在盆边
There's kerosene by the basin
黄帝，好闷吗？
Emperor, are you bore by yourself?
我们来探你
We come to say hello
这个地方是什么人住的？
Who's living here?
我小时候住在这里
I lived here when I was a child
带金住在这里
Tai-kam lived here
拿点生果过来
Fetch the fruit O.K.
你吃一点
Have some...
看什么？不准把面转过来，哼！
Don't turn around, no peeping
还看？
You're still peeping
你真的不准我把面转过来？
Can I turn around now?
不准！
No!
行了
Okay now
看什么？
What are you staring at?
你怕？
Are you nervous?
真老土
Idiot!
我削一个苹果给你吃
Let me peel an apple for you
你的手抖得这么厉害，让我来
Your hands are trembling. Let me do it
这个是你朋友黄帝？
Is this emperior your friend?
是呀！在我小时候，公公送给我的
Yes! Grandpa gave it to me when I was small
这里的东西很有趣
Everything here is so fascinating
你不把它们全都带到香港去？
Why don't you take them all with you to the city?
有时候，把东西留在旧地方会好一点
Sometimes it better to leave things in their proper place
不用好像我这样子
that way. They don't suffer... like me
你不可以比我早死
Don't die befor me!
如果你死了，有谁照顾我？
Otherwise, who'll take care of me for the rest of my life
浓而暖的情
Intense and warm
盖在柔弱的生命
Love caresses life tenderly
一刹的安祥
A moment of serenity
是我在聆听
Sees me listening
着你轻震的心境
The soft pulses of your heart
缘尽似飘云
Love vanishes like cloulds
那样无助的相认
Helplessly I realise
可变的将来
The future is forever changing
可会仍是我
Will I still be a part
因你变得更起劲？
Of your brighter soul?
记不清多欢欣多少高兴
Countless joy and ecstasy
在脑内在各环境跳着未停
Still dancing in my mind
杀不清分不开的恋爱直到未来
Entangled love unto eternity
虽消失还更丰盛
Gone yet going strong
浓而暖的情
Intense and warm
注在疲乏的生命
Love pours into lifeless mind
可变的将来
In the forever changing future
可会仍是我
Will it still be me
跟你爱火里交拼
Fighting you in the battle of love?
这点爱可会得胜
Countless joy and ecstasy
你想不想知道那天晚上的故事？
Let me tell you the truth about that night
几年前因为要医公公的病
My grandpa was seriously ill several years ago
我向高利贷借了十万元
I borrowed 100,000 from a loan shark company
从那时开始生活就有问题
We suffered a lot from the loan
后来我遇上了曹立三
I was lucky to be saved by Sam Tsao
他是亿万富豪曹万川的独子，交游广阔
The only son of Peter Tsaothe Multi-millionaire
为了公公的生活…
To save grandpa
我就跟他在一起
I lived with Sam
曹立三喜欢奢华的生活
He likes to lead a life of luxury
又喜欢结交黑白两道
He likes making acquaintances with both criminals amd police
接管生意不够半年就已经败了 曹万川一半身家
Less than 6 months he lost almost half of his father's properties
曹万川一怒之下要取销曹立三做经理的职位
His father got so mad he cut off his managerial post
曹万川一向对我好好
But his father liked me
于是曹立三就带着我一起去向他爸爸求情
So Sam bought me home to plead him
谁知道…
and then it happened
谁知就是这样我几乎被你的车子撞到
I was almost knocked over by your car
我装死也袛是不想你卷入漩涡
I deceived you to prevent you from getting involved
回到香港又要面对现实了
When I get back to the city. I have to race up to reallty again
你跟我一起不是现实吗？
the reality is that we're together now
给你自己机会，回去跟他说， 叫他给你一条路
Ask him to let you go
钱我可以代你还
I can pay back the money you owe Sam
不是钱那么简单
It's not that simple
有没有争取过？
Have you tried leaving him?
我做人有原则
I believe in certain things
每做一件事都不会轻易放弃
Like, never giving up
不要，哽死你呀！
Don't choke yourself to death!
不到黄河心不死，你听过没有？
Where there's a will there's a way
最多我回去跟他说，你干嘛这么凶？
Take it easy, I'll talk to him
三哥，泰国好不好玩？
Brother Sam, how was the trip to Thailand?
CECILIA，不见半年，很漂亮呀！
Cecilia, you look great!
三哥艳福无边嘛
Brother Sam always gets the best in life!
没人好像CECILIA对我这么好
Cecilia is the nicest of them all
我差不多当她是我的半个老婆
I treat her as half a wife
那另一半呢？
Where's the other half then
另一半就在今天晚上去找
I'll look for her tonight
今天晚上再说
We'll chat about it tonight
怪不得别人说三哥是最幸福的王老五
No wonder Sam's the happiest bachelor in this world
CECILIA在三哥心目中是最有地位的
Cecilia plays a vital role in brother Sam's heart
她很乖，所以我最疼她
She's a good girl. I love her the most
我去了几天有没有想着我？
Did you miss me when I was away?
三哥，到了
Brother Sam, here we are
三哥，我有点要紧的事想跟你到 写字楼去商量一下
Brother Sam, we've to talk privately. It's urgent
不如阿红先送唐先生回酒店去好不好？ 好呀！
Hung, you check Mr Tong in at the hotel Okay!
唐先生，记着今天晚上开局
Mr Tong, Don't forget the party tonight
拜拜！CECILIA
Bye, Cecilia
是不是真的有正点的介绍我？
You've got a special surprise for me
别耍我   一起走吧
Don't kid me Sure, Let's go
正点！做得好！
Good! You did a great job!
阿豹，我去了泰国两天， 有没有替我盯着阿红？
Pow, did you keep an eye on Hung when I was away
有呀！
Yes
那她做过什么事？说给我听听
Tell me what she did
没什么，她昨天去大屿山探她的公公
She went to Lantau to see her grandpa
那么昨天大屿山的天气怎么样？
How was the weather in Lantau?
天气！？
Weather!?
天气不错
Not bad
老板
Sir
豹，帮我开了它
Pow, open it for me
幸亏陈律师机警，不然让人家剃了 眼眉也不知道
Luckily Chan is smart otherwise I'll be make to look a fool
三哥，是我的错
Brother Sam, it was my fault
对不起！没事吧？   没事
Sorry. Are you alright? Yes
阿豹，不必那么认真
Pow, don't take it so seriously
现在连你也受了伤，还有谁替我办事？
If you keep injuring yourself. Who will look after me?
三哥，这个臭小子很串…
Sam, that bastard
干一杯
Cheers
三哥，我会干掉那个小子
I'm going to killthat bastard
干掉你…
I'll kill you
你又想玩什么？
What are you looking for?
我要干掉那个小子
I'm going to killthat bastard
不要呀！你会变成杀人凶手
No, You'll become a murderer
其实那个人对CECILIA是真心的
That guy really loves Cecilia
如果你有他一半那么痴心
If only you were half as true to me as he is to Cecilia
我就心满意足了
Then I'd be the happiest girl in the wrold
不行！谁对不起三哥，我就干掉他
No, I have to get kid of whoever harm Sam
不要说这种话，我跟你喝酒
Forget it, let's drink
你为我喝了这一杯酒
Drink it for me
为了你，干杯！
For you, cheers
再喝一杯
One more
就算为了你杀人，我一样愿意
I'd sacri fice anything for you too, even my life
阿敏…
Mann
三哥，我有很要紧的事要跟你说
Sam, I've something very important to tell you
三爷    谢谢
Master Sam Thank you
我要决定，决定
I got to go though with it
三哥
Brother Sam
又跟谁通电话？
Who was that?
是阿敏
It's Mann
我有点事情要跟你商量
There's something I want to talk to you about
好啊！我最喜欢跟你谈心事
Fine, I love listening to your personal affair
我想…
Well...
这一个洋娃娃跟了我们很久啦？
This doll has been with us for quite a long time
四年了
It's been 4 years
旧了，不如送给别人
It's getting old. Let's give it away
好啊！
Fine!
你知不知道我刚才到那里去了？
You know where I've been?
去坟场呀！买了一束花拜LILY
The Cemetery! I brought a bunch of flowers for Lily
你知道谁是LILY？我的旧女朋友
You know Lily? My old girlfriend
对！是我玩腻了她
I was tired of her.
但是她也不应该勾引我的司机
But she shouldn't have seduced my chauffeur
私奔，出走
She eloped and escaped
好！我成全了她，送了她去远一点的地方
I let them get far away
送了她去西方极乐世界
To the life hereafter
阿红，你说我有没有待薄过她
Hung, tell me did I ever mistreat her?
她这么做是不是很没有良心？
She acted heartlessly
没良心
She was heartless
什么？
What?
没良心
Heartless
你刚才不是说有话跟我说？
You said you had something to tell me
记不起来了，记起来再告诉你
I've forgotten, I'll tell you when I remember
我希望不是那么重要
I hope it's not that important
CECILIA，我有话跟你说，是关于鸡翼的
Cecilia, it's about Chicken Wing
到厨房里再说
Tell me in in the kitchen
他全都知道了
So he knows everything
怪不得他每一句话都有骨
No wonder he implied something when he talked to me
我替你买了明天早上八点的机票 你想办法走吧
You've got to get out of Hong Kong
离开香港再想办法啦！
I bought tickets for tomorrow's 8:00 flight
我灌醉了阿豹，他醒后就会杀鸡翼
I've made Pow drunk now, but if he gets sober later
没有人可以阻止他
No one can stop him killing people
鸡翼呀
Chicken
是你？
It's you?
你是不是真的想我离开三哥？
Are you willing to help me escape from Sam
当然啦！
Of course!
我有两张明天八点的机票去瑞士
I've got 2 ticket for 8 a.m. Tomorrow's flight to Switzerland
明天早上七点在瑞航柜台见
See you at the check-in counter at 7:15a.m.
究竟你们谈得怎么样？
Are you alright?
见到面再说
I'll tell you tomorrow
三哥出来了
Brother Sam's coming
阿敏，你在这里做什么？
Mann, what are you doing here?
没什么，我有些发票赶着给CECILIA签
I've some urgent invoices for Celilia to sign
我先走了
I'm leaving now
用力一点
Harder
原来你就是为了这个女人去放假享乐呀？
You requested to go off on holiday with that woman
你不会明白的
You don't understand
我不明白，我认识你十多年了
I've known you for over 10 years
我还以为你眼角高
I thought you had high standards
原来你是饥不择食随随便便的选一个
Now I've discovered you don't you just fond of tarts
专门泡这些丑八怪，咸水草，贱男人
you chose a bitch indeed
我们是真心的
We're truly love each other
真心！？
True love?
我说是黑心才真，好像你这样
Fake love!
有阿ANN这么漂亮的私家车你不坐
You've the use of a private car like Ann
你跑到街上选上这些破的士
But you take a taxi, like her
如果我有个像阿ANN那么喜欢你的人喜欢我
If I had a girlfriend like Ann
我真是求之不得了
I'd be satisfied
你就偏不要，在街上选破的士
But you prefer a taxi
你知道的，所有的士都是任人上落的
Anyone can pick up a taxi
五个半就可以起旗， 一起了旗就任坐，笨蛋！
It only costs $5.50 to flag down a tax
你不要再诽谤她
Don't insult her again
好！我不诽谤她…
Okay then... I won't insult her
她是新界的士，横头磡的士， 过海的士   够啦！
She's A New Territories taxi, a tunnel taxi... Enough!
你知不知道这些咸水草没半点秀气
She's like an artificial flower without scent
你是斯文人，干嘛要跟她混上？
You're a gentleman. Why pick her up?
我明白了，我明白她怎么会迷到你了
Well, I know why you so devoted to her
你知不知道？戚近荣先生
You know why, Mr Chi Ken Wing?
为什么？
Why?
你不知道？因为你是鸡翼
Because you're a chicken wing
她是鸡，她是鸡…
and she's a chicken...
鸡！？
Chicken!?
你打我！？你打我！？
How dare you hit me?
我每天早上替你买早餐！你打我…
I bought breakfast for you every day...
我告诉你，我们十几年的友谊到此为止
Listen, my friendship ends here
你自己慢慢后悔好了
You'll regret this
你试碰我一下，你敢还手？ 看我不打破你的头
Don't touch me again or I'll break your head
贱男人！贱男人！
You're cheap, just cheap!
阿红，甜品弄好了没有？
Hung, is the dessert ready?
很快就好了
Nearly!
时间到了
Time's up
红心KING
King heart
光线太刺眼了
The light is dazzling your eyes
到你了
Your turn
有没有？    有我有香烟？
Any cigarettes? Yes, I have cigarette
阿红，拿些香烟出来
Hung, get me some cigarettes
让我去拿
Let me get them for you
我自己去拿，阿红…
It's okay. I'll get them. Hung...
一定是睡着了
She must be asleep
我来发？
I turn to deal?
上车啦！
Get in!
开车啦！
Drive!
我陪阿ANN来送你，你不要表错情， 痴心梦里人
I came with Ann to see you off don't get any wrong ideas,
多谢你！
Thanks!
有什么事打电话或寄信回来！
Call or write us you're in any truuble
我会
I will
这一荸钱你收好一点
Look after the money
千万别让那一个坏女人知道呀？
Don't tell that woman about the money
有什么事用来傍身也好
It's oin case of emergency
多谢你们！
Thanks!
什么多谢？即日起钉，三分息
For what! There's 30% interest on it
这一巴掌还给你，无数
We're even now
你是怎么开车的？
What a lousy driver!
调头！谢谢你！
Go another way please
走啦！时间到了
Go
再见！
Goodbye!
没什么事吧？
Is everything alright?
命运注定
It's fate
再见！
Goodbye!
北帝街，发生车祸
A traffic accident in Pak Tai Street
的士
Taxi
司机，请你快一点
Driver, please hurry
我可以换下一班机吗？
Can I change to the next flight?
对不起！八点钟，办登机手续
Excuse me! 8 o'clock, check in
对不起！已停止服务了
No, sorry, it's closed
请问CECILIAYAU在机上吗？
Excuse me! Ls Cecilia Yau on the flight?
我记得她刚换了十点钟班机
Oh! I remember she just changed to the ten o'clock flight
十点钟起飞，谢谢！
10:00 o'clock, thank you!
看着…
Watch out!
快点
Hurry up!
干什么？
What are you doing?
鸡翼
Chicken Wing
放开我！鸡翼
Let me go. Chicken Wing
你说什么？
What did you say?
搅定他们了
We caught them already
他们查到这件事是阿敏搅鬼
We found out that Mann betrayed us
死丫头！食碗面，反碗底
What a bitch who bite's the hand that feeds her
算了吧！我以后介绍一个更漂亮的给你
Forget her! I'll get you another prettier girl
撞她！
Run her down
你撞倒了人就这么跑了
The bastard is going away
喝了它，让你有多远就去多远
Drink up, then you're free to go
不要，你放过我们吧！
Please let us go!
你给我的钱和珠宝，我全都还…
I'll return everything you gave me
不是钱的问题
Money is not the problem
问题在那里，我想你该知道
You know what the problem is
你以为可以随便杀人？
You think you can get away with murder
错，不是我杀人，是你们两个自杀
Wrong, it's not murder, it's suicide
明天报纸就会大字标题
I can imagine tomorrow's headline
说年青男女效法罗蜜欧与茱丽叶 服毒自杀殉情，多浪漫
Young Couple kill themseleves like Romeo & Juliet
罗蜜欧先生，你先喝好吗？
Remeo, you drink first
你个口好臭
You've got bad breath!
喝了它就闻不到了
Drink it and you won't smell it
你害我好了，不要害阿红
Let me drink Poison me but not to her
不是我害她，是你害死她
You're poisoning her, not me
如果不是你这个臭小子出现
If you hadn't appeared
阿红会乖乖的留在我身边
She'd have stuck to me
你太自私了，女人对你来说袛是一个玩偶
Girls are just toys to you
你要多少有多少
You can have so many
这个玩偶是我的
This doll is mine.
你有什么资格把它抢走？
You've no right to take it away from me
喝了它！
Drink it!
不要呀！
No!
你口口声声说爱阿红， 你是不是为了她什么都肯做？
You love her that much, prove it
舔净它！
Lick it!
不敢吗？
Scared?
怕死呀？   不要呀！
Scared of death? No!
没胆量！？
No guts
我可以为阿红，什么都肯做
I'm ready to do anything for Hung
可以杀阿敏，可以杀任何人，你舔呀！
I'm willing to kill Mann or anybody. Lick it up
来呀！
Come on!
阿豹，搅定他！
Pow, kill them
你不要呀！
Don't!
我不会让你死得舒服的
You're not going to die that easily
你杀了我，好让我去陪阿敏
Kill me, so I can join Mann
你疯了吗？
Are you mad?
我不是说过找一个比阿敏更好 的女孩子给你？
I promised to find you a prettier girl
阿敏不同其他女孩子
Mann was different from other girls
阿敏算是什么女孩子？
Different? Mann was cheap
我的女人这么好都可以杀， 何况杀死这个贱人
I'm willing to kill Hung, why not Mann?
你说什么？
Shut up
事实如此，她是贱
It's true, she really was a tramp
连我也够胆出卖的就是贱女人
One that dares to betray me is a tramp
我说得对不对吗？
Am I right?
你不要再说
Shut up
怎么你不觉得她贱格吗？
You don't believe she was a tramp
住口！
Shut up!
我早知道你反骨啦！
I knew you'd betray me!
走呀！
Run her down
回来！
Come back!
快点！
Quick
快点！走呀
跳下去！
Jump!
阿红！
Hung!
我想我可以做的事暂时袛有这么多
I didn't think there's anymore I can do now
医生，我不大明白你的意思
Doctor, I didn't understand
就是说病人的情况现在很不稳定
The patient's condition is very unsteady
她最危险的时期是明天早上
Tomorrow morning is the critical period
如果明天早上她醒过来的话
If she pulls though by tomorrow's morning
我们还有机会
We still have a chance
我们先出去，明天早上再来
Come back tomorrow morning
我想留下来陪着她
I'm staying
医生，他们本来快要结婚
Doctor, they were planning to get married
请你给他一个人情
Please let him stay
O.K.，出去啦！
O.K.
我应承过说不会比你早死
You made me promise not to die before you
我遵守我的诺言
I've kept my promise
但你袛给了我两个月时间，我不够的
But we've been together only 2 months, not enough
我要三十年、四十年！永远呀！
I want 30 years,40years, forever, together
我还有很多事没跟你做
There was so much I wanted to share with you
现在甚至连你走了我都不知道
I wasn't aware when you died
你太不公平
You're unfair
太不公平
Too unfair
为什么开心的时候永远都是这么短
Why is happiness so fleeting